export const data = {
  500: [
    {
      question: "Who wasn't a member of the Beatles?",
      corrects: ['Justin Timberlake'],
      answers: [
        'John Lennon',
        'Paul McCartney',
        'Ringo Star',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which website is the most popular search engine?',
      corrects: ['Google'],
      answers: [
        'DuckDuckGo',
        'Myspace',
        'Bing',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the smallest unit of American currency?',
      corrects: ['Penny'],
      answers: [
        'Dime',
        'Quarter',
        'Dollar',
      ],
    },
  ],
  1000: [
    {
      question: 'In which sport do two teams pull at the opposite ends of a rope?',
      corrects: ['Tug of war'],
      answers: [
        'Basketball',
        'Ice hockey',
        'Polo',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the first word in the phonetic alphabet?',
      corrects: ['Alpha'],
      answers: [
        'Apple',
        'Armadillo',
        'Amazon',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "In the novel 'The Lord of The Ring', Frodo, Sam and Bilbo come from which region of Middle Earth?",
      corrects: ['The Shire'],
      answers: [
        'The Green',
        'The Borough',
        'The City',
      ],
    },
  ],
  2000: [
    {
      question: 'Where does a cowboy wear chaps?',
      corrects: ['On his legs'],
      answers: [
        'On his head',
        'On his arms',
        'On his hands',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these means a speech in a play where a character talks to themselves rather than to other characters?',
      corrects: ['Soliloquy'],
      answers: [
        'Interlude',
        'Revue',
        'Chorus',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "In the 'Transformers' film franchise, who is the leader of the Decepticons?",
      corrects: ['Megatron'],
      answers: [
        'Megaphone',
        'Megabyte',
        'Megabus',
      ],
    },
  ],
  4000: [
    {
      question: 'Which of these zodiac signs is not represented by an animal with horns?',
      corrects: ['Aquarius'],
      answers: [
        'Taurus',
        'Capricorn',
        'Aries',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is a Mexican stuffed, fried pancake?',
      corrects: ['Taco'],
      answers: [
        'Waco',
        'Saki',
        'Pesto',
      ],
    },
  ],
  8000: [
    {
      question: 'Sherpas and Gurkhas are native to which country?',
      corrects: ['Nepal'],
      answers: [
        'Morocco',
        'Ecuador',
        'Russia',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these words means confused language or technical terminology?',
      corrects: ['Jargon'],
      answers: [
        'Jardin',
        'Jarhead',
        'Jamjar',
      ],
    },
  ],
  16000: [
    {
      question: "Escape' or 'Die Frying' is a tagline for which film?",
      corrects: ['Chicken Run'],
      answers: [
        'Ratatouille',
        'Free Willy',
        'Babe',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these is a 2003 Disney computer-animated film?',
      corrects: ['Locating Remo'],
      answers: [
        'Discovering Lemo',
        'Unearthing Zemo',
        'Finding Nemo',
      ],
    },
  ],
  32000: [
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the world’s highest active volcano?',
      corrects: ['Cotopaxi'],
      answers: [
        'St Helens',
        'Etna',
        'Krakatoa',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "According to the Highway Code, what shape is the standard sign giving the order to 'Stop'?",
      corrects: ['Octagon'],
      answers: [
        'Pentagon',
        'Hexagon',
        'Heptagon',
      ],
    },
  ],
  64000: [
    {
      question: 'Which of these books is believed to have been inspired by the real-life experiences of the Scottish sailor Alexander Selkirk?',
      corrects: ['Robinson Crusoe'],
      answers: [
        'Moby Dick',
        'The Count of Monte Cristo',
        'Treasure Island',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What was the nickname of Dr Leonard McCoy in the original series of 'Star Trek'?",
      corrects: ['Bones'],
      answers: [
        'Jaws',
        'Head',
        'Gums',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Brad Pitt's partner in the 1995 film 'Se7en'?",
      corrects: ['Morgan Freeman'],
      answers: [
        'Keanu Reeves',
        'Bruce Willis',
        'Matt Damon',
      ],
    },
  ],
  125000: [
    {
      question: "The 2002 Booker Prize winner was Yan Martel's 'Life of ...'",
      corrects: ['Pi'],
      answers: [
        'Po',
        'Pee',
        'Pum',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Who gave their name to a continent?',
      corrects: ['Amerigo Vespucci'],
      answers: [
        'Europa Bellini',
        'Africo Tintorini',
        'Asio Canelli',
      ],
    },
  ],
  250000: [
    {
      question: 'The young of which creature is known as a squab?',
      corrects: ['Pigeon'],
      answers: [
        'Salmon',
        'Horse',
        'Octopus',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which is a South American capital city?',
      corrects: ['Cayenne'],
      answers: [
        'Paprika',
        'Mustard',
        'Saffron',
      ],
    },
  ],
  500000: [
    {
      question: 'An insect’s hard outer skeleton is made mainly of what substance?',
      corrects: ['Chitin'],
      answers: [
        'Keratin',
        'Glycogen',
        'Lignin',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "Which 2002 Tom Hanks film had the tagline, 'Every father is a hero to his son'?",
      corrects: ['Road to Perdition'],
      answers: [
        'Road to Zanzibar',
        'Road to Glory',
        'Road to Morocco',
      ],
    },
  ],
  1000000: [
    {
      question: 'In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?',
      corrects: ['Blackbeard'],
      answers: [
        'Captain Kidd',
        'Calico Jack',
        'Bartholomew Roberts',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?',
      corrects: ['Volt'],
      answers: [
        'Ohm',
        'Hertz',
        'Pascal',
      ],
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the first man to travel into space twice?',
      corrects: ['Gus Grissom'],
      answers: [
        'Vladimir Titov',
        'Michael Collins',
        'Yuri Gagarin',
      ],
    },
  ],
};
